[
  {
    "text": "q. What did the router say to the doctor \n a. It hurts when IP.",
    "question": "What did the router say to the doctor",
    "answer": "It hurts when IP.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["network"]
  },
  {
    "text": "If you put your ear to a UNIX shell, can you hear the C?",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "A programmer had a problem. He thought to himself, 'I know, I’ll solve it with threads!' \n has Now problems. two he",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "The best thing about a Boolean is that even if you are wrong, you are only off by a bit.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["data"]
  },
  {
    "text": "!false \n (It’s funny because it’s true)",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "An SQL query walks into a bar, approaches two tables and asks, \n \"Hey, can I join you?\"",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["data"]
  },
  {
    "text": "If doctors were like software engineers, \n they would say things like “Have you tried killing yourself and being reborn?”",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "A UI is like a joke... \n If you have to explain it, it's not that good.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "[\"hip\", \"hip\"] \naka. hip hip array",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["data"]
  },
  {
    "text": "Three SQL databases walked into a NoSQL bar. \n They left because they couldn't find a table.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["data"]
  },
  {
    "text": "99 little bugs in the code, \n99 bugs in the code, \n1 bug fixed...compile again, \n100 little bugs in the code.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["bugs"]
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why do Java devs have to wear glasses? \n a. Because they don't C#.",
    "question": "Why do Java devs have to wear glasses?",
    "answer": "Because they don't C#.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the programmer quit his job? \n a. She didn't get arrays.",
    "question": "Why did the programmer quit his job?",
    "answer": "She didn't get arrays.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "Programmer (noun): \n A machine that turns coffee into code.",
    "question": "Programmer (noun)",
    "answer": "A machine that turns coffee into code.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "q. What do you call a programmer from Scandanavia? \na. Nerdic.",
    "question": "What do you call a programmer from Scandanavia?",
    "answer": "Nerdic.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/14/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript"]
  },
  {
    "text": "q. What's the object-oriented way to become wealthy? \na. Inheritance.",
    "question": "What's the object-oriented way to become wealthy?",
    "answer": "Inheritance.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/14/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text": "Debug (/dēˈbəɡ/): \n Being a detective in a crime movie where you are also the murderer.",
    "question": "Debug (/dēˈbəɡ/)",
    "answer": "Being a detective in a crime movie where you are also the murderer.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "12/11/2018",
    "tags": ["bugs"]
  },
  {
    "text":
    "q. Why did the child component have such great self-esteem? \na. Because its parent kept giving it `props`!",
    "question": "Why did the child component have such great self-esteem?",
    "answer": "Because its parent kept giving it `props`!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"]
  },
  {
    "text": "q. How do you comfort a JavaScript bug? \na. You console it.",
    "question": "How do you comfort a JavaScript bug?",
    "answer": "You console it.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "bug"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards? \na. Because they use a strongly typed language!",
    "question": "Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards",
    "answer": "Because they use a strongly typed language",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "java", "c#"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did the functional component feel lost? \na. Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!",
    "question": "Why did the functional component feel lost?",
    "answer": "Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why was the JavaScript developer sad? \na. Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!",
    "question": "Why was the JavaScript developer sad?",
    "answer": "Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "node"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did the developer go broke? \na. Because he used up all his cache!",
    "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
    "answer": "Because he used up all his cache!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did the React Higher Order Component give up? \na. Because it sur-rendered to the prop-aganda!",
    "question": "Why did the React Higher Order Component give up?",
    "answer": "Because it sur-rendered to the prop-aganda!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "When a JavaScript date has gone bad, \"Don't call me, I'll callback you. I promise!\"",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "Dev1 saw a strange JavaScript function & asked, \"What is this?\". \nDev2 responded, \"I don't know. I would've called you, but I was in a bind\"",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript"]
  },
  {
    "text": "Two JavaScript developers walked into the variable `bar`. \nOuch!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap? \na. Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request.",
    "question": "Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap?",
    "answer": "Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks? \na. Because they needed JavaScript experts!",
    "question":
      "Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks?",
    "answer": "Because they needed JavaScript experts!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost? \na. Because he couldn't find his source without a map!",
    "question": "Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost?",
    "answer": "Because he couldn't find his source without a map!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "coffeescript"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. How did the doctor revive the developer? \na. The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!",
    "question": "How did the doctor revive the developer?",
    "answer":
      "The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["css"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did the C# developer fall asleep? \na. Because he didn't like Java.",
    "question": "Why did the C# developer fall asleep?",
    "answer": "Because he didn't like Jav\na.",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["java", "c#"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor? \na. Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!",
    "question": "Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor?",
    "answer":
      "Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "knockout", "backbone"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings? \na. Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\"",
    "question": "How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings?",
    "answer":
      "Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\"",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["css"]
  },
  {
    "text":
      "q. Why was Ember.js turning red? \na. Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!",
    "question": "Why was Ember.js turning red?",
    "answer": "Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!",
    "author": "enphnt",
    "created": "11/11/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "ember"]
  }
]
